and summer vacation will start.
As the head teacher, I,
Uchiyamada,
thank you for your enthusiasm
in teaching.
The only disappointment
has been
the one embarrassment
of a teacher,
to have his class boycotted by
his own students...
This was an unheard
of disgrace.
On top of that,
we would have figured he
would have taken some
of that to heart, it seems he
thinks that summer vacation
has already started!
In any case, come fall he will no
longer be with this academy.
So it doesn't really matter.
That aside, what I want
to say is...
Sorry, I'm in the middle
of a staff meeting right now.
Excuse me.
Hello, did you get the tickets?
You did!
That's great!
Okay! Now I can go to Saipan
and get rid of all this stress
I've built up in Japan!
Now I have a request
of the teachers,
I know that it is considered
that your duties are done.
He's still at it!
The head teacher's so long
winded, you know.
People who're only thinking
of playing,
they want to hurry
and go home.
And so, heading toward fall,
I would like you to consider
what effect you can have.
Thank you very much!
- Oh, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- Yes?
- Could you stay for a bit?
- But... I'm kind of in a rush...
The head teacher has
something important to discuss.
What is it?
We'd like you to teach a special
advanced English class.
- Special advanced class?
- Yes.
During summer vacation,
selected students
from this academy, they'll attend
special classes set up with
a special curriculum for
the college entrance exams.
Didn't you hear about it?
But isn't that same as
the cram schools?
It's those cram schools that
we won't lose too!
If even one more student
gets into college,
then the parents will
be overjoyed,
and this academy's image
will go up!
I'm impressed sir, those who
truly love this academy
- really think differently.
- No, no, please!
Excuse me, but why me?
Teshigawara-sensei
recommended you.
What?
With Fuyutsuki-sensei's help,
I felt I could give it my all.
Congratulations!
Those of you here have been
selected as the top elite
of this academy.
That goes without saying.
We have only one goal.
That is to get you into a first
class university
to build a shining future for you!
In order to achieve that,
we teachers are willing
to sacrifice our summer vacation
and work with you
toward that goal.
If you put your trust into me,
you will make it into
a first class, no...
you'll make it into Tôdai
University. I promise that!
Now then...
When the PTA sees the success
of this special class,
their opinion of me will
undoubtedly rise!
If that happens...
Then someday this chair
will become mine.
No...
Maybe even by fall!
Then my wife and daughter
of mine won't be able
to make a fool of me!
What is it that you want
to talk about?
Well...
Why did you select me?
That's because I thought you
were most suited for it,
- of course.
- But I'm not brilliant like you,
Teshigawara-sensei.
Well, I know the most
about you.
Have more confidence
in yourself.
But...
You see I made plans
to go on a trip.
I'm sorry, but could you ask
the head teacher
to excuse me from this?
Could it be...
- with Onizuka-sensei?
- What?
Are you going on a trip
together?
Of course not! It's with a friend!
Who'd go with that kind
of fool who mistakes
summer vacation a day early?
He's a great conscientious
teacher!
He's probably working
on convincing his students
- to return to class by fall.
- I doubt it!
He's probably somewhere
chasing after some
women's butt right now.
- What are you doing?
- Oh! You surprised me!
Aren't you even embarrassed
as a teacher to be peeping?
That's not what I'm doing, look.
Nomura-san's started
dance lessons!
That's great!
Isn't it, Onizuka-sensei?
- Hmm, look at it jiggle...
- What are you looking at?
Well you know, bigger isn't
always better.
- Just what are you looking at?
- For me, that much is fine.
Onizuka-sensei!
I'm home, Azusa...
SORIMACHI TAKASHI
MATSUSHIMA NANAKO
KONDÔ YOSHIMASA
ENJÔJI AYA
NUMATA BAKU
KOBAYASHI MASAHIRO
IDA KUNIHIKO
KIRARI
IKEUCHI HIROYUKI
YAMAZAKI YÛTA
TOKUYAMA HIDENORI
KUBOZUKA YÔSUKE
NAKAMURA AIMI
KIMURA TAE
FUJIKI NAOHITO
MABUCHI ERIKA
TATEISHI RYÔKO
NAKAO AKIRA
SHIRAKAWA YUMI
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
AKABANE HIROSHI
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Two tickets to Saipan
for the end of the month.
I'll see what I can do,
but it might not be
possible this late.
I'm really sorry!
I really meant to go next week.
But then this special class
thing started.
They come up with some
strange ideas, don't they?
Why don't you quit
this school thing?
But if I quit now in the middle
of the year...
You should take early retirement,
- to get married!
- That'd be great, but...
It's Saipan! Shouldn't you
go with a guy?
Azusa, there must be tons
of guys you
could get to take you.
But wouldn't we be staying
in the same room?
It'll be okay, guys nowadays
are pushovers.
You just have to say
"That's not what I had in mind,"
and they'll give up.
Well, I suppose so, but...
Come on, isn't there some guy?
Like maybe the teacher that sits
next to you in the staff room.
Next to me?
Will you stop that!
Are you going on a date?
He asked me out during
one of the flights.
He's a dentist.
And he's the eldest son.
Maybe I'll keep this one.
It's great being a stewardess.
- You have your pick of men.
- It's nothing great.
There aren't any good
men out there.
You know, to find someone that
you can really say, "I love him!"
- That would be great.
- Sure...
But in reality, there's no men
like that out there.
In any case,
we just have to pick from
the men we find.
- Okay, I gotta go!
- Oh! I'll see you out!
Thanks!
Dammit! Why's it so frickin' hot!
Think I'll buy A/C!
You have that kinda money?
Man! This is the first time
I've got a serious job,
- and I don't even get a bonus!
- Yeah well, you and money were
never meant to be together.
Oh yeah, I wonder what
Fuyutsuki-sensei's going to do?
- Going to do?
- For summer vacation!
I bet she's got lots of plans.
- She must have some guy too.
- Will you cut it out!
- What about you?
- 'Bout what?
Could it be...
you're in love with her?
Are you joking? Gimme a break!
Yeah, that's true. There's no way
a barbarian like you,
and an angel like Fuyutsuki-
sensei would ever get together.
Well 'xcuse me!
Alright then! I'm going
to make a serious play for her!
You got a problem with that?
Of course not!
'Sides, I'd rather have A/C
than a woman.
A/C, huh?
I would like all of you
to witness the great effort
being put into this special
advanced class.
Class is about to start,
please step this way.
Onizuka! Just because your
room doesn't have A/C,
you cannot violate the sanctity
of the principal's office!
It's inexcusable!
If the board saw this, do you
know what would happen?
Teshigawara-sensei is working
so hard with the special class!
Just what are you going to do
about this, Director!
But Onizuka-sensei's class
is boycotting him,
he must be trying to work
a solution out.
He's not doing that!
He was watching adult video's
in the principal's office!
Here's what we'll do...
We'll have Onizuka-sensei stay
here as a security guard.
He does know karate...
What are you suggesting,
Director!
That's right, our police
patrolman is out with
a head cold, so it should
work out perfectly!
- That's not the point!
- Oh my...
I have a plane to catch,
you see - I'm going to visit my
daughter in London for a bit.
Director!
Men are stronger, right?
Everyone knows that.
Hey kid! No jumping!
No jumping, right?
Hey! I said no jumping!
What are you doing,
Onizuka-sensei?
Fuyutsuki-sensei, do you want
to go for a swim too?
- Hold on a minute.
- There's no way I can do that!
It'll be okay!
Here, you can rent a swimsuit!
You're interrupting the special
advanced class!
What's that, the special
advanced class?
Never mind already!
I don't have time for this!
Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Fujitomi-sensei!
I figured considered region?
Alright, calm down everyone!
People who go to second
rate colleges,
end up with second rate lives.
Let them have their fun now.
The one's to have the last laugh,
will be us.
That Onizuka's messing around.
You should just forget about him.
He's only got one more month.
Thanks for your work today.
Oh, Teshigawara-sensei,
you're still here?
Yes, I was thinking of revising
the special advanced class'
curriculum.
Wow, that's great!
I'm no good with machines,
so I've never used PCs.
PCs are easier to use
than it looks.
If you like, I'll teach you
how to use it!
Please!
I think the time has come
to computerize
all the students' personal
information.
With accurate grades recorded
for each individual,
it will enhance the efficiency
of the teachers job.
Wow, that's great!
So, what do I do after this?
Well, you see...
- I'm sorry!
- Oh, that's okay...
Oh, by the way...
if you're not busy, would you
like to get something to eat?
We could discuss PCs
in more detail.
- I'm sorry, not today...
- Oh, I see.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, not at all!
Don't worry about it!
Oh ho!
- What are you two doing?
- What about you?
- Well, I'm the security guard!
- Hey! That!
Isn't that a policewoman's
tablet?
Oh yeah, Teshigawara-sensei!
Could you teach me!
You can watch AVs
on PCs, right?
- You mean AV homepages?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Let's see, you do this...
And then pick whichever
girl you like.
Great!
So how do you look
at other places?
Excuse me!
Will you please stop it!
Lighten up! Hey, why don't you
join us, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- It'll be computer training!
- Don't be silly!
We're going out
for dinner together,
- right Teshigawara-sensei?
- What?
Oh, yes! That's right!
Well then, Mr. Security Guard,
we're counting on you.
Let's go.
If you'll excuse us.
This is so surprising!
I didn't think you'd like
a place like this.
You think so?
I hate formal places.
Music too. I listen
to Mariah Carey
- and Céline Dion all the time.
- Really? Me too!
I always thought you'd
like classical music.
That's what people think,
but that's not how I am.
Even the novel that's most
impressed me lately.
Shinoda Setsuko's
Onnatachi no jihâdo.
Oh yes! That was really
interesting, wasn't it?
- You read it?
- Yes!
It portrayed the feelings
of women so realistically.
You know, I can't believe we
have so many common interests.
Really!
Man, I'm tired!
Really?
Teshigawara-sensei,
your father works
- for the Ministry of Education?
- Yes.
So, is that what you are
aiming for also?
No, unlike my father, I'd rather
remain teaching in the ranks.
Why is that?
Nowadays, observing things
from above, like my father,
does no good.
Times now demand hands
on innovation in education.
If you do that, I believe it will
raise the level of all the children,
and the level of all of Japan.
The children now are lost.
We the adults are
to blame for that.
We can't turn our eyes
away from that.
Is something wrong?
I feel a little embarrassed now.
I'm a teacher too, but I haven't
thought about that at all.
Oh, yes...
Next time, would you like to go
somewhere that has good wine?
Yes, certainly.
- Good morning!
- Oh, good morning!
Teshigawara-sensei!
- Thanks for last night!
- Oh, not at all!
- I had a good time.
- Me too.
- Good morning.
- What are you up to?
I'm a guard, so I have
to make my rounds.
Oh right, I'm sure.
You were probably sleeping
until now anyway.
I have to commend you.
Even though it's summer,
you come to school
for the students' sakes.
You are the shining model
of a teacher!
Of course! Please don't
categorize me with
- the lazy people like you.
- Well excuse me!
And I was going to make you
some tea.
That's quite alright.
When you pour, it looks bad.
That's okay, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
We need people like Onizuka-
sensei for some variety.
- Right on, Tesshî!
- Tesshî?
Well I have class now.
- If you'll excuse me.
- Good luck!
Do you want to go down
to the ocean,
- like in Beach Boys?
- What are you talking about?
Or if you don't want
to be out in the sun,
how about spending the whole
day singing at a karaoke box?
Oh, but before that,
since I'm hungry,
how about a breakfast date
at Yoshigyu? I've got a coupon!
This! Isn't this is a coupon
for a "love hotel!"
Now why the heck do I have
something like this...
Having people like you around
is a really bad influence
on the students.
Please go home!
Yeah, but you don't want
to do this either.
You want to quit this special
advanced class, don't you?
That's how I felt at first,
but now I want to do this,
thanks to Teshigawara-sensei!
Oh I see, the elite...
Onizuka-sensei, you should
learn a thing or two
- from Teshigawara-sensei.
- What?
Well I teach according
to my own policy.
Then let me ask you this,
what does education
- mean to you?
- Well, you see...
Summer vacation isn't
for studying,
you should go out
and play, right?
I can't believe a person like you
is in the same place
as Teshigawara-sensei.
If you like Tesshî so much,
you should date him!
Oh! Maybe I should date him...
Teshigawara-sensei has
similar interests,
his family is rich,
and he's kind,
unlike someone I know...
Do whatever you want!
Be my guest!
You should go ahead
and get it on with
Teshigawara tonight.
You're terrible!
Teshigawara-sensei isn't
crude like you!
Besides, nowadays there are
men who won't do anything
even if you stay together
in the same room.
Well you know...
I think if I ever got together
alone with a woman,
something is bound to happen.
So how many women have you
bedded by saying that?
Sorry, but I've never done
anything like that before.
- Liar! It's true!
- Ask Saejima!
What?
What? No way!
That's because I've decided
I'll do it only with the woman
I've decided is the one!
Yeah right! I bet you
just can't get any!
You should talk,
you don't have any guys.
Sorry to disappoint you,
I have no shortage of men.
There's the man
in import-export,
the advertising company,
the apparel company...
What should I do,
there's too many to keep!
What's with this "keep"?
Men aren't objects!
Marriage is a critical decision
in the life of a woman!
What's wrong with being careful
about selecting your partner?
Don't try twisting words.
Do you enjoy stringing along
and playing with men like that?
If you're going to say that,
then you shouldn't try
to seduce us!
Men are just nice because
they want some!
You're terrible!
You know, I wouldn't go out
with you if you were
- the last person alive!
- That's my line!
Why would I ever go out
with a guy like you!
I ain't gonna listen
to a woman like you!
I don't ever want to see
your face! Get out of here!
No need to ask!
I intend to leave!
Oh! That man! I hate him!
You've got to be kidding!
Are you okay?
I've gotten my hands
on a '82 Chambertain.
If you'd like, would you like
to come over and try it?
What a year! But with this,
I'll be set!
Mama!
- Do we have any edamame?
- What?
Just get some out of the fridge
and zap it.
- I'm home!
- Oh, welcome home!
It's a disaster! It's pouring!
You know, tomorrow, members
of the PTA are going
to be reviewing the special
advanced class.
They will witness the success
of this marvelous class.
It'll be a success for education!
It'll reflect on my reputation!
Oh, really?
- And so?
- You see...
You see, if the board sees this,
then by fall I'll be principal!
Really!
- That's great!
- Well, yeah.
Oh, I'll get it!
Let's see,
shall I make you a snack?
I'm so glad, Papa!
You were always saying you
would, but it never happened.
I'd almost given up!
Oh, you've had to suffer too.
That's okay!
And so...
When you become principal,
how much will your salary go up?
I'll finally be able to buy
that Chanel bag,
I've been resisting all this time!
That's right, when you become
principal, you'll need a new suit.
Hello, Yoshirin?
It's me!
My daughter is not here now.
Nuts, it's her Dad!
Oh, then I'll call back later.
Excuse me,
but what kind of relationship
do you have with my daughter?
Well, we just met,
so I'd say we're friends,
yeah, friends.
Now listen,
don't you dare lay a finger
on my daughter!
Understand?
Hey! What are you doing, Papa?
- Don't call again!
- Wait!
Hey!
Who was it!
It was that useless bum.
You're terrible! How rude
to answer someone else's phone!
I'm just concerned for you.
- He's a worthless man!
- I'm going to date him for sure!
Yoshiko!
- Mama, tell her...
- It really has been a long time!
You see, my husband is going
to become principal!
Oh my! It's still too early for that!
I've heard that voice
somewhere before...
God, what an old fart!
But you know, I think I've heard
that voice somewhere before...
Oh well, time for patrol.
You keep it quite clean,
don't you?
It's like there isn't a single
speck of dust!
- Please...
- Thank you.
I'm just careful not to get it dirty.
Can I listen to a CD?
Please, go ahead.
This song!
I've been listening to just
that lately.
It's a good song, isn't it?
- What's in here?
- Oh, that's the bedroom!
It's a mess, so I keep it locked.
Oh, excuse me!
Ore wa otoko da! and
Yûhi ga oka no sôridaijin.
Whew, this stinks!
This is just like Hakamada-sensei!
And you've watched Kinpachi...
Whew! Gross!
Hurry and close it! It stinks!
Wow! Check out Kotani's!
Hey, isn't this all
confiscated stuff?
- Hey! Gimme that!
- Don't be such a snoop!
Oops! I saw...
in rush?
But staff room?
Hold it!
Don't look in Fuyutsuki-sensei's.
I'll check it later!
- Yes, sir!
- Onitchi!
Teshigawara's won't open!
- Lemme see.
- Tesshî's, huh...
That's just like Tesshî.
Alright, I'll open it!
What's this?
Excuse me, I should be
going home.
The trains should still
be running.
Oh, but... Then how about
having just a glass of wine?
But...
I bought it just for you,
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Well, okay, just one glass.
Thank you.
Oh! It's good!
- It really is different, isn't it?
- Isn't it?
Thank you very much.
I...
Now is the beginning...
Our night together.
I...
I've been dreaming of this.
With no one to interfere.
To confirm our ultimate
love together.
This...
It's fate.
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
What is it?
I wanted to ask you something,
- Teshigawara-sensei.
- Could you make it tomorrow,
I'm about to go to sleep.
- It'll only take a minute!
- What do you want?
You see, I wanted to check out
these foreign porn sites,
but I couldn't figure this out.
I figured you were the only one
who could figure it out.
You have a PC, right?
Could you teach me?
- Hey! Hold it! Wow!
- What an unreal condo!
Rent must be expensive!
Okay, alright.
I'll show you, so please
go after that.
Thanks.
Establish the reference
to the server,
then follow what's written
in the manual.
I don't understand what you're
doing, but you're amazing!
Okay! If that's all,
- then please leave!
- Okay already! I'm going!
Is there something you still
don't understand?
Isn't this wine expensive?
Like ten thousands of bucks
- or something like that?
- Well, yes.
Could I try some?
I've never had any before.
- It's nothing special.
- Will you please go on home!
Okay! I'm going! I'm going!
I got it!
- You've got a woman over!
- What are you talking about?
Don't play innocent,
- I saw you had two glasses.
- Well, that...
Why don't you introduce me...
Never mind and go home
already!
Okay! I'm going!
- Right after this!
- Hey! Stop it!
I told you to go home!
I see.
So that's your game.
So here's the question...
Who do you feel the most
sorry for?
One...
Fuyutsuki-sensei who has been
given wine with a sleeping drug.
Or two...
The Tôdai graduate Teshigawara-
sensei who can only get
a woman through
cowardly means.
Or three...
The students who look up to that
teacher while studying hard
in the special advanced class.
If you want to get a woman,
you should risk all
your life for her.
Onizuka-sensei!
That damn Onizuka!
Your hand, is it okay?
It couldn't be helped.
I never thought Teshigawara-
sensei would do
something like that.
When it comes down to it,
why are men all like that?
Do they want sex that badly?
It's despicable!
It's because men are all like that,
that women have to decide
to either keep or run from them.
- What are you doing!
- Your eyes are rotten!
You go into a man's room
without thinking.
You accept presents without
thinking.
It's because you play with men's
feelings like that.
That's why your eyes
became rotten
and you can't see men
in any other way.
All you can do,
is compare them with your
friend's boyfriends,
and compare status!
If you enjoy that, then go ahead!
Love isn't about status.
I don't want you to be like that!
What with all this "keep"?
Hello, this is Fuyutsuki.
Miyuki?
It's about those tickets.
I'm sorry,
I can't make it.
No...
It's just that there's things
going on at school.
I'm really sorry.
Okay!
That looks good on you.
What?
Your outfit today.
But you know, I think you're
better in a skirt, like yesterday.
Why's that?
Your underwear was pink,
wasn't it?
- You looked!
- Your butt felt so nice and soft.
Why you!
Why are you always like that!
So what do you think?
The attentiveness and
seriousness of this class.
The teachers and students
are working together
to get into first rate universities.
Sir,
isn't n and z switched around?
Oh my,
looks like the learning
goes both ways.
Why don't you take things
seriously for once!
Oh shaddap already!
That angry face doesn't suit you,
Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Hold it! There's something
I have to tell you!
What is it?
Please ignore that!
It isn't anything!
This is so idiotic!
Which university you get into,
is of no concern to me!
What special advanced
class crap!
It's so stupid!
If you want to study so much,
then go and study
by yourselves!
Teshigawara-sensei!
I'm sorry, there must be
some mistake!
Please wait here!
Teshigawara-sensei!
Probably, Onizuka got to him.
You know you!
Why were you talking
so big last night?
What did I say?
Oh I know, you like the water,
don't you, Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Hey!
Wait you!
Why that...
What's up with that Onizuka?
He's only got another
month anyway.
- He'll be gone soon.
- I can't wait that long.
I'll kill him, that Onizuka!
2016-04
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app